https://ammunitionstore.com/privacy-policy/

Sign in or Create an account
Loading... Please wait...
Pistol Magazines
View All...
Rifle
Pistol
Looking for ammunition that we may not have in-stock?
Would you like to
receive news about our ammo?
Sign up for our bullet points newsletter
today by entering your information below!
Your First Name:
Your Email Address:
AK-47
AR-10 .308 Cal.
Browning 1919A4
223 - 5.56 M27 (M249 SAW, FN Minimi, Shrike)
308 - 7.62 NATO M13 (M60, M240, M134)
Miscellaneous
Federal Premium Ammunition Wolf Performance Ammunition Remington Military Surplus Speer American Eagle Glock Lapua CCI Minutemen USA
Ammunition Store Privacy Policy
Your personal information is treated as strictly confidential.
When you sign up, or make a purchase, with Ammunitionstore.com none of your information leaves our servers. You are not put on any lists, or submitted to any databank.
Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate, disclose and make use of personal information. We will safeguard any personal information unless sharing that information is required to comply with a criminal investigation.
The following outlines our privacy policy.
Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
We will collect and use personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and agreed to by the customer.
We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, all records should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
We will protect personal information by reasonable and proven security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.
Advertising Privacy
We do not share or disclose any of our customer information. We do not use any customer information for 3rd party marketing. We do not participate in any spam mailing or bulk mailing. All email lists generated are on an opt-in basis, such as our newsletter or promotional opt-ins.
Credit Card Privacy
We do not store credit card information on our web servers. This is for your safety and protection. We do not offer any marketable information to any third party contractor or group. All transactions are done through encrypted https services and are secured with SSL (secure sockets layer) technology.
All prices are in USD.
Copyright 2020 Ammunitionstore.com.
Sitemap
Shopping Cart Software by BigCommerce
